cityweekly.net 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy / Terms of Use | Salt Lake City Weekly

**Privacy Statement:**

The purpose of this policy is to document the rights and confidentiality afforded to all the visitors to the City Weekly web site (www.cityweekly.net). City Weekly follows the procedures set forth below to safeguard your privacy on-line. Please read the following policy to understand how we handle your personal information. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Receipt of E-Newsletter**

As a registered user of the City Weekly web site, you will receive CW E-Newsletter. CW E-Newsletter is a weekly newsletter from City Weekly highlighting new weekly content. If you prefer to not receive this weekly update, just click [unsubscibeLink] to opt out at any time and you will not receive this update again.

**When do we ask for personal information?**

An anonymous visitor to our site remains anonymous. We do not attempt to identify visitors if they do not voluntarily register on our site.

**How personal information is collected and distributed**

For some areas of our website, we may collect personal information from you. In these cases, we intend to inform you in advance and grant you the option not to continue. The City Weekly web site collects no personally identifiable information unless provided explicitly by the user. If you choose not to provide the requested information, you still can access most of the City Weekly website; however, you may be unable to access certain options, such as use of the message board, comments, classifieds, Best of Utah voting, etc.

City Weekly manages and catalogs all its information gathered off the website with care. All information collected at this site is kept strictly confidential and is not intended to be shared, commercially sold, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed to persons other than City Weekly representatives.

**Use of Cookies:**

Some of our web pages incorporate the use of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that travels to your browser from a web server and is stored on your computer's hard drive.

City Weekly uses cookies for storing user IDs for specific web pages. We provide a cookie for your convenience to enable an enhanced experience on our site. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you still have access to all of our web pages; however, you may be forced to re-register every time you visit certain areas of our site that require such an action. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Privacy of our email lists**

For various reasons, we may ask that you supply us with an email address in order to participate in certain features on our web site. City Weekly does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any of the addresses on our list to anyone outside of City Weekly. 

City **Weekly Classifieds and Message Board Guidelines:**

City Weekly reserves the right to remove any classified ad or message board listing without notice, warning or refund. 

City Weekly does not control the content of the classifieds ads or message board listing, nor does it guarantee the accuracy or quality of the content. Users of this system understand that by browsing City Weekly Classifieds, that you will be reading content that could be objectionable to you. Under no circumstances will City Weekly be liable in any way for any classified ad or message board listing, including, but not limited to: any errors or omissions in any ad, any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content posted in the City Weekly Classifieds.

**Use of this site indicates that you agree to the following:**

• To never sell anything illegal. 

• Fully and accurately describe your service or sale item. 

• You are entirely responsible and liable for any content you post or any content that is posted through your account. 

• You will follow these terms and guidelines. 

• City Weekly reserves the right to modify or discontinue any and all parts of the site, all without notice even though such changes may change the way you use the site. You agree that the City Weekly shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the classified listing and display system. 

**Responses to legal process**

Notwithstanding the foregoing, if City Weekly receives due legal process, City Weekly may disclose information provided to us through our web site. 

**Questions:**

City Weekly welcomes comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information. Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this site. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [webmaster@cityweekly.net](mailto:webmaster@cityweekly.net).
